<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE appendix
[
  <!ENTITY % entities SYSTEM "entity-decl.ent">
    %entities;
]>
<sect1
 xml:id="app-cf-operator-values-yaml"
 xmlns="http://docbook.org/ns/docbook"
 xmlns:xi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude"
 xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink"
 version="5.0">
 <title>Complete suse/cf-operator values.yaml File</title>

 <para>
  This is the complete output of <command>helm inspect values suse/cf-operator</command> for
  the current &productname; &productnumber; release.
 </para>

<screen>## Default values for Quarks Operator Helm Chart.
## This is a YAML-formatted file.
## Declare variables to be passed into your templates.


# applyCRD is a boolean to control the installation of CRD's.
applyCRD: true

cluster:
  # domain is the the Kubernetes cluster domain
  domain: "cluster.local"

# fullnameOverride overrides the release name
fullnameOverride: ""

# image is the docker image of quarks job.
image:
  # repository that provides the operator docker image.
  repository: quarks-operator
  # org that provides the operator docker image.
  org: registry.suse.com/cap
  # tag of the operator docker image
  tag: v7.1.3-0.g0ce050b

# creates a service account for coredns-quarks, the must be unique as it is used for the cluster role too.
corednsServiceAccount:
  create: true
  name: coredns-quarks

# logrotateInterval is the time between logrotate calls for instance groups in minutes
logrotateInterval: 1440

# logLevel defines from which level the logs should be printed (trace,debug,info,warn).
logLevel: debug

# nameOverride overrides the chart name part of the release name
nameOverride: ""

# workers are the int values for running maximum number of workers of the respective controller.
workers:
  boshdeployment: 1

operator:
  webhook:
    # host under which the webhook server can be reached from the cluster
    host: ~
    # port the webhook server listens on
    port: "2999"
  # boshDNSDockerImage is the docker image used for emulating bosh DNS (a CoreDNS image).
  boshDNSDockerImage: "registry.suse.com/cap/coredns:0.1.0-1.6.7-bp152.1.19"
  hookDockerImage: "registry.suse.com/cap/kubecf-kubectl:v1.19.2"

# serviceAccount contains the configuration
# values of the service account used by quarks-operator.
serviceAccount:
  # create is a boolean to control the creation of service account name.
  create: true
  # name of the service account.
  name:

global:
  # Context Timeout for each K8's API request in seconds.
  contextTimeout: 300
  # MeltdownDuration is the duration (in seconds) of the meltdown period, in which we
  # postpone further reconciles for the same resource
  meltdownDuration: 60
  # MeltdownRequeueAfter is the duration (in seconds) for which we delay the requeuing of the reconcile
  meltdownRequeueAfter: 30
  image:
    # pullPolicy defines the policy used for pulling docker images.
    pullPolicy: IfNotPresent
    # credentials is used for pulling docker images.
    credentials: ~
      # username:
      # password:
      # servername:
  # monitoredID is a string that has to match the content of the 'monitored' label in each monitored namespace.
  monitoredID: cfo
  operator:
    webhook:
      # useServiceReference is a boolean to control the use of the
      # service reference in the webhook spec instead of a url.
      useServiceReference: true
  rbac:
    # create is a boolean to control the installation of rbac resources.
    create: true
  singleNamespace:
    # create is a boolean to control the creation of resources for a simplified setup
    create: true
    # name is  the name of the single namespace, being watched for BOSH deployments.
    name: staging

quarks-job:
  serviceAccount:
    # create is a boolean to control the creation of service account name.
    create: true
    # name of the service account.
    name:
  persistOutputClusterRole:
    # create is a boolean to control the creation of the persist output cluster role
    create: true
    # name of the cluster role.
    name: qjob-persist-output
  singleNamespace:
    createNamespace: false
</screen>
</sect1>
